celticfc.net 2003-10-02

# Soccer - Celtic Football Club - Glasgow - Scotland - Privacy Policy

This web site is owned and operated by Celtic plc. We take the security of your personal information very seriously.  Celtic plc are registered to process personal information in terms of the Data Protection Act 1998 and we will observe appropriate security procedures in relation to our obtaining, holding, transfer and other processing of your personal information. We will at all times seek to comply with our obligations under the Data Protection Act 1998 

This Privacy Policy explains how Celtic plc will use the personal information that we collect from you and how we will keep your personal information secure. Please take the time to read this policy carefully.

**Younger Fans and the Huddle Club **

If you are a younger fan who is under the age of 16, you must first ask for the consent of your parent or guardian if you are using this web site. Any persons under 16 providing information to Celticfc.net should not submit any of this without express parental or guardian consent.

Personal information about members of the Huddle Club is not, under any circumstances, passed to third parties. If you are under 16 we suggest that you do not submit any personal information such as your postal or e-mail address or telephone number to any open forum.

**Uses and Disclosures of your Personal Information **

We collect personal information about you via Celticfc.net to allow us to administer this web site, to help us provide a service that meets your requirements and expectations **,** and to inform you about news, events and developments at Celtic Football Club. 

We will send you information by e-mail about other products or services that we offer and which we think will be of interest to you. 

We will send you information by e-mail about the products or services of certain carefully selected third parties whose goods or services we think will be of interest to you. 

**You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you or giving your details to others for these marketing purposes.   Please e-mail us at customerservices@celticfc.co.uk or write to us at Customer Services, Celtic Football Club, Celtic Park, Glasgow, United Kingdom, G40 3RE, if you wish us to stop.** 

We will also use your personal information to conduct market research surveys and to carry out statistical analysis with a view to improving the quality of the services that we offer to you.

**Use of Cookies **

We use “cookies” to identify you, to make your visit to the Celticfc.net site more enjoyable and to build up a demographic profile.  A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser that enables the server to collect information back from the browser.  We use cookies to identify users and personalise their visit by customising our web pages for them.

**Security of your Personal Data **

As the Internet is not a secure medium of communication, we cannot guarantee the security of any information which either you or any other party transfers to us via the Internet.  Any e-mails which we send to you and any e-mails which you send to us or to which we reply may be intercepted at any time by a third party as such communications will not be encrypted.  Any such e-mail will be deemed, therefore to be non-confidential, and the senders or recipients of any such e-mail by their use of this site accept that those e-mails may be intercepted by other parties.  If you are concerned about interception of personal data about you by third parties, you should reconsider whether you wish to communicate with us by e-mail.  Celtic plc and Celticfc.net is not and will not be responsible for any damages you or any other party may suffer as a result of the loss of confidentiality of any such information. 

**Webcams **

Celticfc.net uses Webcam technology.  Images are live and are not recorded, saved or used by Celtic plc and cannot be passed to any third party for use. Users of this web site can create still images from the webcam camera, and these can only be utilised in accordance with the terms and conditions of use of any information as provided by Celtic plc and Celticfc.net.

**How to Access your Information **

Under the Data Protection Act 1998, you are entitled to receive a copy of the personal information which we hold about you if you apply to us in writing at Celtic plc, Celtic Football Club, Celtic Park, Glasgow, United Kingdom, G40 3RE. A fee will be payable but this will not exceed £10.00.  We will be happy to comply with your request, although to safeguard your privacy we will only supply you with the information to which you are entitled, once you have supplied to us such information as would reasonably be required by us to satisfy ourselves as to your identity. 

If you have any concerns or questions regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us at [customerservices@celticfc.co.uk](mailto:customerservices@celticfc.co.uk) or write to us at Customer Services, Celtic plc, Celtic Football Club, Celtic Park Glasgow, United Kingdom, G40 3RE.
